好了  选一张牌
Okay, pick a card.
好
Okay.
记住是什么牌
All right now, memorize it.
好了没
You got it?
好了
Oh yes.
是这张吗
Is that your card?
就是这张
Yes.
-大家好  -你们好
- Hey guys! - Hi there!
你们猜怎么着  本要拍电视广告了
Guess what? Ben is going to be in a TV commercial!
你们在说什么
What are you talking about?!
还没有最后定下来
Well, it's not for sure but umm,
我们在公园里遇到一个人
we met this guy in the park who
他觉得本很可爱
thought Ben was really cute--
这也是事实啦  总之
y'know, which he is--so umm anyhoo,
他留了张名片  要我们带本
he uh, he gave us his card and told us to bring him down
去参加广告试镜
for this commercial he's auditioning.
这个人是本地最大的广告选角导演
This guy is like the biggest commercial casting director in town!
本去公园随便散个步  就有试镜自动送上门
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition!!
我是说  本  真有你的
I mean, way to go Ben!
那个公园我都去烂了
Man! I've been in that park a million times
从来没人主动找我去试镜
and no one offered me an audition.
真的很神奇  我们只是在陪本玩荡秋干
I know, it's crazy! We were just pushing Ben on the swings...
我每次都在玩荡秋千啊
I'm always on the swings!
我是哪里做错了
What am I doing wrong?!
荡秋千
That.
我要走了  祝我好运
Okay, gotta go! Wish me luck!
祝你好运
Luck!
瑞秋  既然现在你在拉夫·劳伦上班
Hey Rach, now that you're working at Ralph Lauren,
能不能帮我带几件马球衫回来
can you bring me back some of those polo shirts?
知道吗
Uh well, y'know what?
第一天上班就偷公司东西  我可能下不了手
I don't think if I feel comfortable stealing on my very first day...
不愿意慷公司之慨  有意思
Unwilling to steal from work, interesting.
就算有人能拿免费的  那也非我莫属
Besides, if anybody's gonna get free stuff, it's gonna be me.
好了  各位  祝我好运吧
Okay guys, way to wish me luck!
祝你好运  给他们瞧瞧厉害
Good luck! Go get 'em!
好了  来讨论下帮瑞秋庆生的事
Okay, let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
我建议在周末办惊喜派对
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
可是一个月后才是她生日啊
Whoa-whoa, but her birthday isn't like for another month.
是没错  但在生日当天开派对
Yeah but if we throw her a party on her birthday,
那就不惊喜啦
then it's not a surprise.
好主意
I think it's a great idea.
我们办个晚宴  只邀请好朋友过来
Yeah, we could have a dinner party and just invite her close friends.
罗斯  我们要帮瑞秋办惊喜派对
Ross!! We're having a surprise party for Rachel!!
好
Okay!!
搞定
Done.
好的  你想我们合办吗
Okay, great so do you want to do it together?
乐意之至
I would love to do it together!
她们要一起办哦
They're gonna do it together.
兄弟  这位可是我女朋友
Dude! That's my girlfriend!
所以我就得闭嘴吗
What, so I gotta shut it down now?
好了  我得走了
All right, I gotta take off.
我要接本去参加大试镜
I'm picking up Ben then we're off to the big audition.
看到有演员假装是本的父亲
It's gonna be weird to watch some actor
那种感觉一定很怪
pretending to be Ben's dad.
是啊
Yeah.
怪过看他的两个妈妈亲热吗
Weirder than seeing his two moms make out?
爸爸  广告里面有爸爸吗
Whoa-whoa dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
是啊  本和爸爸喝汤  演得很陶醉的样子
Yeah the dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
或许我可以跟你们一起去
Whoa, hey, maybe I'll go down there with ya
搞不好能试镜演那个爸爸
and see if I can get an audition to play the dad.
扮演本的爸爸  自然是我这教父最适合了
I mean who better to play Ben's father than his godfather.
你不是本的教父
You're not his godfather.
什么
What?!
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?!
当然是啊
Of course I am!
我们走吧  教父
Okay, let's go godfather.
好的
All right!
我获选了  他们让我试镜
Hey! I'm in, they're gonna let me audition!
真的  太棒了
Really? That's great!
就是  选角导演中有个女的
I know! I know! It turns out that one of the casting ladies
看过我的演出  所以我离她离得远远的
has actually seen me in a play, so I steered clear of her...
那个孩子看起来很眼熟
Hey, that kid looks familiar.
是啊  他拍过一堆广告
Oh yeah, yeah! He's done tons of commercials.
有麦片广告  游戏机广告
I've seen him in like Sugar Smacks, Playstation,
还帮电话公司拍过广告
and that one for the phone company.
他演得实在是太好了
In fact he was so good in that one,
我索性跟着换了电话公司
he actually convinced me to switch phone companies.
钱德勒因此还气得半死
Chandler was mad....
不过他这次休想拿到这角色
Yeah well, he's not gonna get this one.
因为本比他可爱多了
Ben is way cuter than that kid.
看就知道  看看你
I mean look at him, look at you,
很好
That's great.
如果我能演本的爸爸是不是很棒
Listen, wouldn't it be great though if I got to play Ben's dad?
乔伊  你跟本一点都不像
Joey, you look nothing like Ben.
比你跟他像多了
I look more like him than you do!
我跟你还没熟到那个程度
Y'know, I don't really know you well enough for you to do that.
现在是最后的二选一
So it's down to these two,
南茜  我知道你喜欢这一个  我也喜欢
Nancy I know you like this one and I think I agree.
瑞秋  你觉得呢
Rachel, what do you think?
那个是很漂亮
Well umm, that one is pretty but uh,
但我超爱这个的质料  抱歉了
I just, I just love this fabric  Sorry.
不用抱歉  提供意见是你的职责
Oh don't be sorry, that's part of your job here to give your opinions
功劳归我  开玩笑的
and then I take credit for them--I'm kidding.
她是在开玩笑  但下次可别跟她唱反调了
She is kidding, but don't ever disagree with her again.
这次换我开玩笑了
Okay, now I'm kidding!
这个办公室真有趣
Oh, what a fun office.
我不知道要选哪一个
I don't know which one,
不过先来根烟倒是真的
but I do know I need a cigarette.
不如我们出去休息一下
So what do you say we take a break, we go outside,
等回来之后再解决
and we'll figure this out when we come back?
瑞秋  你抽烟吗
Rachel? Do you smoke?
不抽  我爸是医生
Oh no, my dad's a doctor
老跟我说些恐怖的故事
and he would always tell me just horror stories......
说那些妖魔鬼怪
about ghosts and goblins
完全赞同公主抽烟
who totally supported the princess's right to smoke.
她们在抽烟的时候
...and then they came back from smoking
就背着我做出了决定
and they had made all of the decisions without me!
这样太不公平了
That doesn't seem fair.
就是  好像我被惩罚了
I know! It's like I'm being punished
就因为我没有恶心又伤身的抽烟习惯
for not having this disgusting, poisoning habit!
对  抽烟最棒了
Yeah, it is the best.
万一这种事没完没了怎么办
I mean what if this keeps happening?
她们在外头抽烟做决定
Y'know, they'll-they'll be outside smoking, making all the decisions
我只能在办公室里呼吸愚蠢的新鲜空气
and I'll just be up in my office breathing my stupid clean air,
等到了哪天
y'know? And then when the day comes
金姆要选人升职时
when Kim wants to promote one of us,
她会选谁  我还是乌烟瘴气的抽烟女
who do you think she's gonna pick? Me or Smokey Smokerson?
瑞秋  你也可以一起去  不用抽烟
Rachel, you can go down there, you don't have to smoke.
就说要去呼吸下新鲜空气
Just say you wanna get some fresh air.
对  这是个办法
Yeah, I can do that.
你也可以简单点  抽烟就行了
Yeah, or you can do the easy thing and smoke.
瑞秋  要去喝咖啡吗
Hey Rach, you wanna get some coffee?
乐意之至
I would love to!
好
Oh good!
宝贝  我也想一起去
Yeah, I wanna go to babe.
好啊
Oh good.
等等  我变卦了
Oh wait, I change my mind!
好了  来讨论派对的事
Okay, let's talk about the party!
我有一大堆点子
I have so many ideas!
我也是
Yeah, me too!
真是壮观
Oh, look at that.
好了  这是蛋糕的素描图
All right, that's a little sketch of the cake,
还有一些菜单的样本
umm some sample menus,
我在想  前菜可以用
umm y'know what I thought we would start out with
意式的小点  至于音乐呢
Tuscan style finger food, and for music,
这是按字母顺序排列的我CD的收藏列表
here's an alphabetized list of all my CDs!
跟食物超搭配的还做了记号
I've highlighted the ones that would go really good with the food.
不是说要温馨的晚宴吗
What happened to the intimate dinner party?
现在不那样做了
Oh, we're not doing that. Okay...
看来你一手包办了
So wow, it looks like you took care of everything.
多谢了  合办人
Thanks a lot, co-host.
怎么了  我没有一手包办啊
What?! I didn't take care of everything,
你要做的事还有很多
there's-there's plenty of things for you to do!
举个例子
Like what?
杯子
Cups.
杯子  你让我准备杯子
Cups? You're giving me cups?
还有冰块
And ice!
杯子和冰块  我就负责杯子和冰块吗
Cups and ice? Ooh, I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
好吧
All right.
行  我就来负责杯子和冰块
Fine, okay, I will be in charge of cups and ice!
等等  冰块可以从我餐厅拿
Wait a minute, I can get ice at the restaurant...
冰块是我的
I got it! Mine!
试镜顺利吗
Hey! How'd the audition go?!
不太顺利
Not so good.
慢着  你在学乔伊那招吗
Wait a minute, are you doing Joey's
"试镜不太顺利
"Audition didn't go so well.
事实上很顺利"
Yeah it did?"
是很顺利
Yeah I am!
-本取得了第二次试镜的资格  -太好了
- Yeah, Ben got a second audition! - Great!
我得把自己这招教给罗斯
Yeah, I had to teach Ross my bit
因为我没有过关
because I actually didn't get a callback.
你也过关了  对吧
You got a callback too didn't you?
没错
Yeah I did!
瑞秋  你怎么会来这里
Hey Rachel, what are you doing out here?
一个人在上面有点孤单
Oh well, it's kinda lonely up there,
我就想来这里  呼吸下新鲜空气
so I just thought I would come out here and get some fresh air.
南茜和我正在讨论秋装
Nancy and I were talking about the fall collection.
太好了
Oh great!
总之我们要...
So anyway we really...
亲爱的  抱歉  呛到你了
Honey, I'm sorry, we're just smoking all over you.
抱歉
Oh, sorry!
没关系
Oh that's okay.
不成  你待着  我们走
No-no-no, we'll move you just stay right there.
我把设计交给了拉夫
You know I sent the designs over to Ralph
他对这个系列很满意
and he's very excited about the line.
太好了  你是最棒的
Oh that's great! You are the best!
不好意思  能给支烟吗
Excuse me, can I, can I bum one of those?
这支就好
Y'know what, actually...
好啦  你们在聊什么好笑的
Okay, okay, okay, what's so funny over here?
我还以为你不抽烟呢
I thought you didn't smoke.
我以为你们是说大麻烟
Oh, I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes,
毒品那种
Y'know what I mean, like dubbies?
我还纳闷
And I actually, I thought to myself,
她们是疯了不成
"Wow, those guys are crazy!"
这种正常烟  我自己天天都抽
But no, I actually smoke the regular ones all, all the time.
我们很嗨
We get high.
我也是
Oh, me too.
开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我也是
Oh, me too.
老天  这真是折磨人
Oh God, this is so nerve wracking!
你是怎么习惯的
How-how do you do this?
遗憾的是  我得到的复试机会不多
Well, unfortunately, I don't get many callbacks so...
我们在试镜之后被留下来
Is it a good sign that they asked us
这是好现象吗
to hang around after the audition?
天知道
Who knows?
最后入围的是
Okay uh, we have narrowed it down
雷蒙  本  凯尔和乔伊
to Raymond, Ben, Kyle, and Joey.
其余的人  辛苦了谢谢
The rest of you, thank you very much.
好耶  我就知道
Yes!! I knew it!!
拜拜
Bye-bye!
再见
So long!
回见了
Later!
太棒了  我有可能饰演本的爸爸
Oh this is great! I might actually get to play Ben's dad!
事实上那是不可能的
Actually, that can't happen.
因为你们长得太不像了
Yeah because you all have such different looks,
所以你和雷蒙一组  凯尔和本是一组
we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
最后是两组二选一
So it'll be either you two  or you two.
要命  这样就有点尴尬了
Man, this is gonna be kinda weird.
真的是
Yeah, it is.
对  一定会很尴尬
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
因为我们是最好的朋友
No, we-we're gonna be like best friends,
所以才会尴尬
that's why it's gonna be weird.
原来如此  我只是答腔而已
Oh, oh, I thought we were just talking.
瑞秋生日派对前  这些东西放这里好吗
Is it okay if I leave this stuff here 'til Rachel's birthday party?
当然可以  里头是什么
Ah sure. What's in 'em?
杯子
Umm, cups.
很好  因为我们替瑞秋准备了八百加仑的水
Oh good, because uh we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
老实说  这些杯子还真不少
Seriously that's a lot of cups.
对  这是因为我负责杯子和冰块
Yeah well, that's 'cause I'm in charge of cups and ice,
莫妮卡一定会后悔莫及
and Monica is gonna rue the day
她要我负责杯子和冰块
that she put me in charge of cups and ice.
我也后悔过一次  除了后悔没做别的
Y'know I rued the day once...didn't get a whole lot else done.
好吧  该把其它杯子搬上来了
Okay, time to bring up the rest of the cups.
-乔伊  -菲比
- Hi, Joey. - Hey, Pheebs.
罗斯  你在这里正好
Ross good, I'm uh glad you're here.
我有事要跟你说
I wanna talk to you about something.
怎么了
What's up?
我一直在想这次拍广告的事
Well, I've been thinking about this whole commercial thing,
我和本要硬碰硬  互相竞争
y'know me going up against Ben, the two of us competing,
这样不会有好结果
and that can't lead to anything good.
我想我还是退出好了
So, I think I'm just gonna step aside.
告诉他们我不去试镜了
I'm gonna tell them that I won't audition.
乔伊  太好了  多谢
Wow, uh, Joey that's-that's great. Thanks man.
就这样  你真要让我这样做吗
That's it? You're-you're gonna let me do this?!
这可是事关我的职业生涯
This-this is my career we're talking about here!
可是你刚...
Well, you just...
我是要套你说出让本退出
I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it!
罗斯  如果真有人要退出  那也应该是本
Look Ross, if anyone should step aside it should be Ben!
什么
What?!
钱德勒  告诉他为什么
What? Chandler! Tell 'em!
我先去开门
Well I mean, let me get the door first.
没有人  你好
Oh, hi! No one.
本为什么应该退出
Why should Ben step aside?
这原本就是他的试镜
It was his audition in the first place!
你是跟过去的  就像是跟班老爹
You-you just tagged along! You're like the uh, tag-a-long dad.
起码我有顾虑到本的感受
At least I care about his feelings!
什么
What?!
你知道万一他没通过试镜  会有多难过吗
Do you know how hard this is gonna be on him when he doesn't get it?
那他又为什么不会通过呢
And why wouldn't he get it?
得了吧
Oh, come on!
你没看到跟我同组的小子有多厉害吗
Have you seen what my kid can do?! Huh?!
他会拨电话  吃玉米脆片
I mean he dials phones! He-he-he eats tortilla chips!
还会和卡通老虎踢足球
He-he plays soccer with the cartoon tiger!
你是说  你的小子喝汤比我儿子厉害
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
给他汤匙你就瞧好吧
You just give him a spoon baby!
是吗  我们走着瞧
Oh yeah? I guess we'll just see!
好啊  这支广告非我和米奇莫属
Yeah! Because this commercial belongs to me and Mitch!
你的孩子叫做雷蒙
You're kid's name is Raymond!
对  你的也是
Yeah?! So's yours!
工作怎么样
How did work go?
很棒
Oh it was great!
太棒了  我按你们说的去了她们抽烟的地方
It was great! I went down there just like you said, y'know?
我们讨论公事  金姆完全接受我的意见
And we talked business. Kim totally took my opinions.
你好臭
You stink!
多谢
Thanks!
我是说真的
No, I'm-I'm serious!
因为那里的人全都在抽烟
Well-well that's 'cause I went down there and they were all smoking.
这其实是成功的味道
This is actually the smell of success.
不过有点怪怪的
Okay, there's something different though--
天啊  你有抽烟
Oh my God! You smoked!
我没有
I did not!
你抽了
Yes you did!
你看起来快乐又病态  你一定有抽烟
You look happy and sick; you smoked!
好啦  我有抽  为了事业不得已
All right, fine! But I had too! I had to do it for my career!
好羡幕
I wish I had smoked for my career...
这样很恶心耶
That's so gross!
没那么糟啦
No well, no it's not that bad, y'know?
虽然舌头有点打结
I mean yeah, my tongue feels a little fuzzy
手指也有点怪昧
and these fingers sort of smell,
其实我感觉快吐了
I actually feel like I can throw up.
但你一定要撑过这一关
Okay, but you gotta push past this
再来就会是乐无比了
because it is about to get so good!
钱德勒
Chandler!
你浑身烟味  我得去透透气
I have to tell you, you smell so smokey I have to get up.
我说真的
I'm not kidding.
我觉得你闻起来很香
I think you smell great!
所以大家都同意了
So, we're decided,
不要格子图案  要粉红
no on plaid, yes on pink?
完全正确
Absolutely!
我举双手双脚赞成
I am so on board!
瑞秋  这支烟不是才刚点吗
Rachel didn't you just light that?
是的  但是
Yeah, I did, but y'know what?
我正在努力少抽烟
I am really, really trying to cut back, y'know?
"瑞秋  祝你好运啦"
Good luck, Rach.
其实我最近有想要戒烟
I've actually been thinking about quitting lately.
那可不  我每周日晚上都告诉自己要戒烟
Oh sure, every Sunday night I'm telling myself
结果周一还不是狂抽猛抽
I'm quitting but every Monday morning it's like
可不是嘛
Tell me about it!
那就戒了吧  我们一起戒烟
Well then let's just quit! We'll just quit! Let's all quit!
听起来是很诱人
It does sound appealing.
我戒烟从没成功过
Oh, I never could do it.
你可以的  一定行
Oh but you could. You can. Absolutely!
我们可以互相帮助  用那个什么
We can help each other out! We can get--
戒烟贴  我们能组成戒烟贴三姐妹
what are those--those patches! We could be like the Patch Sisters!
其实我们真的应该戒烟
Oh y'know, we really should quit.
好吧  一起来戒烟
Okay, let's quit!
太棒了  把香烟给我  统统交出来
Yes! Great! Give me those cigs! Give it! Give it!
不抽了
Done, quit!
那个打火机是我先夫送我的
My late husband gave me that lighter.
我没在开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
那好吧
Okay then!
嗯  汤
Hmmm, soup!
Hmm soup!
嗯  汤
Hmm, soup!
乔伊  罗斯马上就来了
Joey, Ross is gonna be here any second,
我去下洗手间  帮我看一下本好吗
would you mind watching Ben for me while I use the ladies' room?
好啊  没问题
Oh yeah, no problem.
谢谢
Thanks.
本
Hi, Ben.
你想当演员吗
So you wanna be an actor huh?
告诉你  很辛苦哦
I gotta tell ya, it's no picnic.
有碰不完的钉子
There's tons of rejection.
一点都不稳定
No stability.
前一天你还是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
One day you're Dr. Drake Remoray,
隔天你就要抱着瓶子吃番茄酱
the next day you're eating ketchup right out of the bottle.
乔伊
Joey!
罗斯
Ross!
本
Ben!
本  本
I mean, Ben! Ben!
雷蒙  乔伊  该你们上场了
Okay, Raymond, Joey you're up.
好吧  我们来试一次
Okay, uh well, let's try one.
你们准备好了就开始
Whenever you guys are ready.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
这是面汤  我练习时用的是番茄汤
Well this is noodle soup and uh, I've been working with tomato.
不过没关系  没问题的  嗯  面汤
But that's okay, no problem. No problem. Hmm, noodle soup.
你那样不错  不过台词是"嗯  汤"
Y'know, that's-that's fine, but the line is, "Hmm, soup."
那我刚才说什么
Oh, what did I say?
嗯  面汤
Hmm, noodle soup.
有什么不一样
How's that different?
好  我们来试一次
All right, let's try one.
嗯  面汤
Hmm, noodle soup.
好  我们再来一次
Okay. Let's do it again.
好
Okay.
嗯  汤
Hmm, soup.
我是说"面汤"  不对  是"汤"
I mean, noodle soup. I mean soup!
有没搞错
Come on!
我们得换下一组了
Y'know what? We need to move on.
不  我再演一次
No! No! I-I can do it one more time! See?
你看  嗯  面汤  可恶
Look!  Hmm, noodle soup. Damnit!
被逮到了
Uh-oh, busted!
你们这是在干嘛
Come on you guys! What are doing?!
我们不是戒烟贴三姐妹吗
I thought we were the patch sisters!
完全没用
Yeah. That didn't work out.
瑞秋  我们有试着戒烟  但实在是太难了
Rachel we tried to quit, but it was too hard!
你们开始抽烟
Well y'know if you, if you started smoking again
起码也该告诉我嘛
you could've at least told me!
快点来一支  刚才说到哪里了
Come on, give me one of those! What are we talking about?
不行  你戒烟很成功
No. No! You're doing great!
不许放弃
Don't you give up!
所以我们才没跟你说
That's why we didn't tell you
我们不想拖你下水
and we're not gonna drag you down with us.
等等  别这样  拖我下水吧
Oh wait, no-no-no! Drag me down. Drag-drag me down.
瑞秋  万万不可
Forget it Rachel!
你戒烟成功我们都替你骄傲
We're both so proud of how well you're doing.
我不能让你前功尽弃
I'm not gonna let you blow it.
若被我发现你抽烟  我一定炒你鱿鱼
In fact, if I catch you with a cigarette, you're fired.
走吧  离开这里
So go on, get out of here!
我不要你吸二手烟  快走
Go on, I don't want you breathing this stuff! Go on!
好了  你和我一起去法国出差
So, okay! So you'll come with me on the Paris trip.
要命
Oh man!
你瞧瞧  杯子帽  杯子横幅  杯子灯
Check it out! Cup hat! Cup banner! Cup chandelier!
还有本尊  杯子
And the thing that started it all, the cup!
菲比  你对杯子还真有一套
Great job with the cups, Pheebs!
你干脆跟她去约会得了
Why don't you just go out with her!
你有没有注意到冰  各式各样的都有
And did you notice the ice? Look! We have it all!
有碎冰  冰块  还有干冰  注意看
We have crushed! Cubed! And dry! Watch!
很有神秘感吧
Mystical!
钱德勒  没人吃我的法式小点心
Chandler! Everyone--no one's eating my Tuscan finger food
他们全跑去吃菲比的冰甜筒了
'cause they're all filling up on Phoebe's snow cones!
有冰甜筒吗  冰甜筒  好恶心
There are snow cones! Snow cones! Yuck!
你去吃啦
Y'know...go! Go! Right there!
谢谢
Thank you! Thank you!
她回来了
Oh, look! Look! Look!
惊喜
Surprise!!
什么啊  一个月后才是我生日啊
What?! What?! My birthday's not for another month!
这样才惊喜啊
That's the surprise!
天啊  这真是太棒了
Oh my God! You guys this is so great!
我完全没想到
I mean it's so unexpected!
钱德勒的生日还在我前面呢
I mean Chandler's birthday is even before mine!
惊喜
Surprise!
真是太棒了
Wow! This is so great!
看看这些杯子
Look at all these cups!
真是怪怪的
This is so weird.
杯子是我负责的
I was in charge of cups.
那就没那么怪了
Oh, okay, not so weird.
我很遗憾你试镜不顺利
Listen man, uh, I'm sorry the audition didn't go so well.
是哦
Yeah right!
乔伊  我是真的很遗憾
No really, I-I am Joey! I feel bad!
罗斯  你用不着遗憾
Yeah? Well look Ross, you don't have to. Okay?
是我自己差劲  怨不得你
It's not your fault I suck.
连"面汤"都说不好还算哪门子的演员
I mean what kind of an actor can't even say, "Hmm, noodle soup."
你知道吗
Yeah y'know what?
或许你搞砸了试镜  不是因为你差劲
Maybe-maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck,
或许你搞砸了试镜
maybe you messed up because you care
是因为你更在意你的教子
more about uh, your godson.
什么意思
What you do mean?
我认为  在潜意识里
I think, sub-consciously...
等等  我听不懂
Wait-whoa-whoa, you lost me.
我觉得在某种程度上
I think on some level,
你搞砸了自己的试镜
you-you sabotaged your own audition
好让本拿到那个角色
so that Ben would get the part.
你的说法比我的好多了
Well, you're way sounds a lot better than mine.
-对  不是我演技烂  -不是
- Yeah. Yeah! It's not that I'm a bad actor... - No!
只是我  太在意小本了
No, it's just ah, I care so damn much about little Ben
看到他成功对我来说更重要
that uh, it was more important to see him succeed.
就是这样  谢谢你
There you go. Thank you!
-谢谢你  那他拿到角色没  -没有
- Thank you! So, did-did he get it? - No.
你又能怎么样
Eh, what are you gonna do?
不好意思  瑞秋·格林在吗
Oh, hi! Excuse me, is uh Rachel Green here?
我跟她约了吃中饭
I was supposed to meet her for lunch.
她现在不会下来这里了
Oh, she doesn't come down here any more.
她在十楼
You can find her up on ten.
好的
Okay, great.
我们午饭时聊到昨天的推介
So we talked about the whole presentation yesterday at lunch
他担心一个人出差
and he wondered if one person would be enough
不够看  我说
to get a take on the trip and I said,
是的  当然了
"Yeah, absolutely!"
后会有期了
I'll catch you guys later.